export const question = {
    1: {
        question: "Eiichiro Oda first wanted to name Sanji ________?",
        options: [ "Oda", "Naruto", "Yonji", "Kenji"],
        ans: '2',
    },
    2: {
        question: "Zoro has one more hobby in addition to sleeping, training, and getting lost. That is ...?",
        options: [ "flipping through new bounties and weapons", "polishing his swords", "fighting strong enemies", "slandering Sanji"],
        ans: '1',
    },
    3: {
        question: "Who is the third smartest character in One Piece from east blue?",
        options: [ "Nami", "Captain Kuro", "Ben Beckman", "Koby"],
        ans: '1',
    },
    4: {
        question: "Chopper was originally supposed to be a ...?",
        options: [ "Zebra Reindeer smoking cigars", "Racoon Reindeer with large antlers", "Bear Reindeer with a white furry belly", "Bull Reindeer chewing on a twig"],
        ans: '1',
    },
    5: {
        question: "One Piece was originally supposed to last?",
        options: [ "8 years", "10 years", "5 years", "3 years"],
        ans: '3',
    },
    6: {
        question: "Which one of the following series was a major inspiration for One Piece?",
        options: [ "Yu Yu Hakusho", "Bleach", "Naruto", "Dragon Ball"],
        ans: '4',
    },
    7: {
        question: "Who is the crew member that Luffy didn't invite?",
        options: [ "Brook", "Robin", "Nami", "Franky"],
        ans: '2',
    },
    8: {
        question: "Every devil fruit has a swirly pattern on it. Why?",
        options: [ "To distinguish them from other fruits", "Because they have special powers", "To make them look cooler", "So that they look more complicated"],
        ans: '1',
    },
    9: {
        question: "Which Devil Fruit power does Oda want in real life?",
        options: [ "Whitebeard", "Robin", "Kizaru", "Luffy"],
        ans: '2',
    },
    10: {
        question: "Why did Oda wanted to become a manga artist?",
        options: [ "Because he had a passion for drawing", "Because he had a passion for storytelling", "Because he was interested manga", "Because he didn't want a real job"],
        ans: '4',
    },
} 